Adobe Product Activation

Product activation is a technical measure that helps protect Adobe against unauthorized copying of its software.  Activation is mandatory.  If you do not activate this product, eventually you will be prevented from using it.  You may be required to contact Adobe Customer Support by telephone in order to activate this product.

No personal information is provided to Adobe or any other party during the activation process.

At the time of installation, this product and your computer create an activation number which, along with the product serial number, is provided to Adobe during the activation process.  Neither the activation number nor the product serial number include personal information or information about the make or model of your computer.  If you activate this product using the Internet, Internet protocol variables required to establish a connection across the Internet are transmitted to Adobe during the activation process.  These Internet protocol variables include your browser type and Internet protocol address.  Adobe does not correlate Internet protocol variables with any personal information.

This product can tolerate changes to your computer's configuration.  Minor reconfiguration of your hardware after activation will not require an additional activation. If you replace or overhaul your hard drive, or if you remove this product from one licensed computer and install it on another licensed computer, you may be required to activate this product.  

Product activation is separate and distinct from product registration.  Product registration is a voluntary process during which you provide Adobe with certain personal and non-personal information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address and product serial number.  All information provided to Adobe during the registration process is stored separately from information provided to Adobe during activation.

For more information about product activation, please visit http://www.adobe.com/activation
